// Questions as Objects 
const questionList = [
    {
        question: "Commonly used Data types do NOT include:",
        choices: ["strings", "booleans", "alerts", "numbers"],
        answer: "alerts"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a logical operator",
        choices: ["*", "=", "!=", "||"],
        answer: "||"
    },
    {
        question: "The condition in an if/else statement is enclosed with _____.",
        choices: ["quotation marks", "curly brackets", "parenthesis", "square brackets"],
        answer: "curly brackets"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a valid JavaScript Variable name",
        choices: ["13reasonswhy", "Teen Wolf", "#blessed", "lastAirbender_1"],
        answer: "lastAirbender_1"
    },
    {
        question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store",
        choices: ["numbers and strings", "other arrays", "booleans", "all of the above"],
        answer: "all of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript which of the following is not considered an error",
        choices: ["dividing by 0", "syntax Error", "missing brackets", "missing semicolons"],
        answer: "dividing by 0"
    },
    {
        question: "String values must be enclosed within _____ when being assigned to variables.",
        choices: ["commas", "curly brackets", "quotation marks", "parenthesis"],
        answer: "quotation marks"
    },
    {
        question: "In ES6, JavaScript introduced 2 types of variables. What are they called?",
        choices: ["let and const", "var and let", "var and const", "none of the above"],
        answer: "let and const"
    },
    {
        question: "A very useful tool used during developement and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
        choices: ["JavaScript", "terminal/bash", "for loops", "console.log"],
        answer: "console.log"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a correct way to declare an arrow function",
        choices: [
            "function sipJuice (juice, flavour) => ", 
            "var buyCoffee = '' => ", 
            "let haveBrunch = food, cost => ", 
            "const eatFood = foodChoice => "
        ],
        answer: "const eatFood = foodChoice => "
    }
]